Hello, Hello brother, friend, I welcome you all to Online Suraj.
In today's video, I am going to
tell you about India Post
Payment Bank.
If you have not applied for India Post Payment Bank's CSP, then
go quickly and apply for India Post
Payment Bank
because India Post Payment Bank has many
services. It is a very good service.
In this video, we are going to tell you in full detail
what services are available in India Post Payment Bank. So let's
cut the video to this, so you
can see here in the fast track.
You can open an account in India Post Payment Bank.
In the first, you can open an account.
After that, you can see below here that you can
deposit cash and
withdraw money in India Post Payment Bank.
India Post Payment Bank account
opening, cash deposit, cash withdrawal, this is done.
After that, we will show you the second service,
money transfer. You
can transfer money 24 hours a day. There is
no time limit for it. And you can recharge and pay bills
from this India Post Payment Bank CSP. And you
can see below the relative service,
account slip service.  You can
update your PAN card, but you can also
get a subscription for the customer.
You all know that you can see cash withdrawal,
balance enquiry, mini statement,
all these services are available in APS,
after that you can see third party
services here, in third party
services you can do life insurance,
life insurance and general
insurance, all these are services in
APK, you can add mutual funds in it,
after that here the financer service is the
main service, in the financer service, if the
mobile number is not linked with the Aadhaar card,
then you can update this mobile number
with Aadhaar and generate a digital life
certificate, you can
make a life problem certificate, which is a bus
certificate, here you can also prepare a bus certificate, you
can pay for these through India Post Payment Bank, post office products, Shukranu
or Sruthi Nidhi, PPF, Words Pay and
RPI
blouse layer, you can pay for these services here through
India Post Payment Bank,
this is the main service, you can
update Aadhaar in the financer service through
mobile number and talk  You can prepare the certificate
and make all these payments. This is a
very good service. If you want to avail it, then
apply quickly and if you like the video, then
subscribe to the channel,
like the video and share it. Thank you
for watching my video.
[Music]